(Emily:)Mmm. It's a beautiful night.
(Raj:)Oh, yes, we've
got the moon
(Raj:)and the trees and...
(Raj:)Elizabeth McNulty,
(Raj:)who apparently died
when she was the same age I am.
(Emily:)Makes you feel
alive, doesn't it?
(Raj:)So does enjoying a meal
at a well-lit restaurant,
(Raj:)but here we are.
(Emily:)You aren't scared, are you?
(Raj:)Of ghosts, no.
(Raj:)Of you, little bit.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry I've
upset you.
(Sheldon:)I shouldn't have asked
so many questions.
(Penny:)No, it's okay.
(Leonard:)Yeah, maybe it's good
you got us
(Leonard:)talking about this stuff.
(Sheldon:)Well, look at that--
(Sheldon:)even when I'm causing problems,
I make the world a better place.
(Sheldon:)Hey, next, why don't we tackle
your penchant for whining
(Sheldon:)and Penny's love
of the ol' glug-glug?
(Penny:)Uh, Sheldon, I think
we're good for now.
(Sheldon:)Ah, well... very well.
(Sheldon:)So does this mean you'll
finally pick a wedding date?